In the last videos, we talked about how
you could read information off of the
HTML page and how you could update what
was on the HTML page. Um, and before we
go further, I'd like to explain a little
bit of the thought process here. So, the
thought process is that most of the apps
that you will build as a web developer
or someone who's programming in
JavaScript are going to be what's called
CRUD apps. CRUD apps, the the acronym
CRUD stands for create, retrieve,
update, and delete. Um, there are people
who will argue that that is the only
type of app in existence. Um, and I've
seen some pretty good arguments for
that. Um, either way, um, a lot of apps
are CRUD apps. You are creating,
retrieving, updating, and deleting
information. So, if you're doing that
with information, you probably want to
reflect that on the page. So, in the
last few videos, I showed you how you
could update the page, and I showed you
how you could read information off the
page. If you're paying attention, that
is two parts of cred. So that leaves us
with um creating information and
deleting information. So that's what
we're going to cover in the next few
videos. And then we're also going to go
a little bit more into the event into
handling events.